Compliance Supervisor III

ROBERT SMITH

Phone: (123) 456 78 99
Email: info@qwikresume.com
Website: www.qwikresume.com
LinkedIn: linkedin.com/qwikresume
Address: 1737 Marshville Road,

Alabama

Objective

To obtain a position in compliance management which allows to put 25 years of varied environmental, safety, and operational experience to use in a setting that combines day-to-day operations, compliance management, and long-term business planning.

Skills

Project Management, Site Acquisition, MS Office.

Work Experience

Compliance Supervisor III

Los Angeles LOMOD Corporation - May 2016 - 2020

- Directs, reviews, evaluates and assesses staff members, including but not limited to workload and performance.
- Assists in development and implementation of goals, objectives, policies, procedures, and priorities for staffing needs for the department.
- Assists in creating Monthly Compliance Department invoice and updating HUD work plans.
- Provides conflict resolution for owners, agents, developers, HUD and other customer representatives.
- Ensures internal policies and procedures regarding state federal procedures are met pertaining to HUD rules and regulations.
- Assists in updating, training and implementation of administrative policies and procedures.
- Implements HUD Rules and Regulations in preparing reports for audits conducted for a
 portfolio with over 725 contracts pertaining to various Section 8 finance programs (i.e LMSA,
 NC, SR, PRAC, 231, 236, 202 etc.) Conduct quality assurance to review the work of peers in
 order to provide guidance and evaluate the accuracy of the Management and Occupancy
 Review and FHEO reports.

Compliance Supervisor

Delta Corporation - 2011 - 2016

- S/Lean audits.
- Continuous improvement program and item implementations.
- Review and revision of procedures and policies.
- Updated and maintained OSHA and University policies for department Facilitated OSHA and University training for all employees Maintained training .
- East Lansing, Michigan, United States, [] Compliance Supervisor, June 2012-Present Responsibilities Meet OSHA and MSU policy and train accordingly/.
- Organized position that is responsible for multiple projects while maintaining appropriate confidentiality Co-operate with other departments Solely .
- Audited closed mortgage files to ensure compliance with federal regulations, supervised and trained staff of 20 auditors and 40 loan officers on .

Education

Masters in Public Administration - January 2008(California State University - Northridge, CA)